<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Orane Marchal</title>
    <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Orane Marchal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dev.oranemarchal.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accueil</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/</guid>
      <description>Bonjour et bienvenue sur mon site ! Je m&amp;rsquo;appelle Orane Marchal, je vis à Paris et je suis Ingénieur en Optique. Après avoir travaillé dans la Recherche Publique sur les diagnostiques optiques pour la caractérisation de plasmas, j&amp;rsquo;ai travaillé dans l&amp;rsquo;étude des Contrôles Non Destructifs par ultrasons. Je travaille aujourd&amp;rsquo;hui pour l&amp;rsquo;industrie automobile en tant qu&amp;rsquo;Ingénieur Design Optique pour l&amp;rsquo;éclairage avant. Vous trouverez plus de détails dans la section « CV » de ce site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curricilum Vitæ</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/resume/</guid>
      <description>Orane Marchal 22 Juin 1986, Paris, Permis B
e-mail
Expériences professionnelles Valeo Vision  Déc. 2011 – Auj.  Bobigny Ingénieur en optiques modules halogène, xénon et LED pour éclairage avant. Design, simulation optique, industrialisation, suivi de production. Formation de collaborateurs.
Ajilon Engineering  2011  Boulogne-Billancourt Ingénieur d&amp;rsquo;études. Participation à la constitution de dossiers de réponses à appels d&amp;rsquo;offres et de propositions de projets, mission de suivi de projet d&amp;rsquo;industrialisation chez Sagem DS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome on my website! My name is Orane Marchal, I live in Paris (France) and I am an Optical Engineer. After working in Public Research on optical diagnostics for plasma characterization, I studied Non Destructive Testing using ultrasounds. I am now working in the automotive industry as an Optical Design Engineer for front lighting. Please check the “Resume” section for further details.
Apart from optics I love music, reading, TV shows and visiting the numerous great museums Paris has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/info/</guid>
      <description>Information Find me  On LinkedIn (en): oranemarchal  Contact  Send me an email: contact Contact me via Twitter: @PetiteRanou  About this website This website has been created using Hugo by Vincent Batoufflet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Informations</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/fr/info/</guid>
      <description>Informations Où me trouver  Sur LinkedIn (en) : oranemarchal  Contact  M&amp;rsquo;envoyer un mail : contact Me contacter par Twitter : @PetiteRanou  Informations sur ce site Ce site a été créé avec Hugo par Vincent Batoufflet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dev.oranemarchal.info/en/resume/</guid>
      <description>Orane Marchal 22nd June 1986, Paris, driver&amp;rsquo;s license
e-mail
Work Experiences Valeo Visibility Since  Dec. 2011  Bobigny, France Optical team member working on halogen, xenon and LED projectors for front lighting. Design, optical simulation, industrialization, production follow-up. Newcomers training.
Ajilon Engineering  2011  Boulogne-Billancourt, France Research engineer. Participation in the establishment of the offers submitted in response to call for tenders and proposed project offers, industrialization project monitoring at Sagem DS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>